rap4.com 2013-08-05

# Real Action Paintball Privacy Statement

| 

**Privacy Statement**   

**_WELCOME_**

Real Action Paintball is  committed to protecting the privacy of visitors to our sites. By using these sites, you agree to the information collection and use practices described in this Privacy Policy. Please do not use our sites if you do not agree to these terms. YOUR CONTINUED USE OF THESE SITES FOLLOWING THE POSTING OF CHANGES TO THESE TERMS WILL MEAN YOU ACCEPT THOSE CHANGES. 

**_ONLINE PURCHASES_**

In connection with purchasing goods over our sites, we ask for such information as name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number and credit card information. This information is used by  Real Action Paintball to process your order. Additional information can be found in our Terms and Conditions of Sale document viewable at the time of purchase. **Before we authorize any online purchase** , we require any customer who desires to buy our airguns, ammunition, lasers, propellants, paintball markers or paintballs over our web sites to either complete a "Create An Account" by clicking on "My Account" or contact us directly. We will retain the information for our records. 

**_SURVEYS, CONTESTS & SPECIAL OFFERS _ **

From time to time we may ask registered visitors to participate in surveys in which we may ask various demographic or product usage-related questions. Also, we may, on occasion, give away our products to randomly selected registered visitors, provided those individuals complete a "Buyers Statement, Affidavit and Verification". Also we may send e-mail messages with promotions, special offers or news letters. In this event the consumer will have an opportunity to request and be granted removal from our mailing list. Participation in these activities is completely voluntary. Survey information will be used for purposes of improving our site, our service and our products. 

**_USE OF COOKIES_ **

A cookie is a piece of data that is sent to a visitor's browser, stored on the visitor's hard drive and contains limited information about the visitor. Real Action Paintball does not collect any personally identifiable information through cookies. Rather, Real Action Paintball uses cookies for various technical purposes associated with the operation and performance of the web site. You are free to reject our cookies if your browser permits; however, this may hamper your access and use of our sites. 

**_USE OF IP ADDRESSES/LOG FILES_ **

An IP address is a number that identifies your computer to other computers on the Internet. When you visit a web site, the web site's server uses your IP address to show it where to download the web pages. Real Action Paintball collect IP addresses for the purpose of system administration, to analyze aggregate information, and to audit the use of our site. We do not, however, link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable. This means that a visitor's session will be logged, but the visitor remains anonymous to us unless the visitor submits personally identifiable data as set forth above. 

**_CHANGING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION_ **

Customers may access your personal information by logging into our system and viewing your profile. If there is information we need to correct, update or modify, you must notify Real Action Paintball by email or U. S. post. If you want to view or correct information about your product registration, please contact Real Action Paintball. To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to verify your identity before updating or correcting any of your personal information. The site administrator will process your request as received. 

**_CHILDREN'S PRIVACY_**

Real Action Paintball do not collect any personally identifiable information from children under 13 years of age. Children under 13 years of age are not permitted to register with our sites. Real Action Paintball, may, however, allow children to participate in online contests offered on our sites. In such case, Real Action Paintball will not collect from the child more information than is reasonably necessary for the child to participate in the activity. Real Action Paintball will ask only for the visitor's e-mail address, date of birth, and, if appropriate, parent's e-mail address. If a child under 13 years old wins, we will send a follow-up e-mail to the parent's e-mail address asking the parent for a mailing address so that we can send the prize. The follow-up e-mail to the parent shall contain a notice advising the parent that he/she may withhold consent for the child to receive the prize. Real Action Paintball will not use the child's e-mail address or other information provided in connection with the child's participation in the contest for any other purpose and shall delete such information from its computers once the contest is over. 

**_SHARING INFORMATION WITH OTHERS_ **

Real Action Paintball may, from time-to-time, share with select third parties both aggregated demographic information as well as personally identifiable information about our customers. We may also gather statistics about the usage of various aspects of our services to help us determine what types of additional services to offer our customers, to otherwise change or enhance the services, or for other internal administrative purposes. We may use an outside shipping company to ship orders, a payment solutions provider to evaluate and process online purchase orders, and have used a fulfillment house to process warranty registrations. It is possible that one or more of these companies may retain, store, share, or use personally identifiable information provided them for secondary purposes not directly related to their provision of services. We may also disclose personal information about you in response to: (a) requests from local, state or federal law enforcement officials; (b) requests by any judicial, administrative or similar proceeding or order, such as subpoena; (c) if required by law; (d) in special circumstances, such as in response to a physical threat or perceived physical threat to any individual; and (e) in the event that Real Action Paintball merges with another business entity or substantially all of its assets related to the products or services which you receive from us are acquired by another business entity, it is likely that customer information will be one of the assets transferred to the other business entity. 

**_LINKS TO OTHER SITES_**

Our sites contain links to third party sites not under Real Action Paintball's control or governed by our Privacy Policy, Terms of Use or Terms and Conditions of Sale. Because these sites may collect information about you, we advise you to check their privacy policies. Real Action Paintball disclaim all responsibility for the operation of such sites, including the information collection and use practices of such sites. Real Action Paintball does not monitor, review or endorse the content of third party sites linked to this site. You acknowledge that Real Action Paintball is not responsible for the accuracy, copyright compliance, legality, decency or any other aspect of the content of such sites. Linking to such sites is at your own risk. 

**_SECURITY_**

Our sites have security measures in place designed to help protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Some features of our sites may require you to use a password. We encourage you not to share your password with others, but if this becomes necessary, please exercise discretion, as you will be responsible for any loss or liability incurred by using our sites through such password. Real Action Paintball recommend you use the latest browsers so as to take advantage of advances in security technology. While on a secure page, such as an order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers, such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes "locked," as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just "surfing." When you enter sensitive information (such as your credit card number), that information is encrypted with an 128-bit encryption protocol known as SSL ("Secure Sockets Layer"). Although we strive to protect your personal information once we receive it, no data transmission over the Internet is completely secure. Visitors must accept all risks associated with any data transmission, including the risk that their personal information may be intercepted in transit. 

**_REVISIONS TO PRIVACY POLICY_ **

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will notify customers on our homepage so they are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

_**IF YOU HAVE QUESTIONS .** . . _

If you have any questions or concerns about our information collection or use practices, please contact us: 

Real Action Paintball  
Attn: Consumer Affairs   
2215 Ringwood Avenue  
San Jose, CA 95131  
Tel.: 408-434-0434
